[
    {
        "front": "あそびます",
        "back": "enjoy oneself, play",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "およぎます",
        "back": "swim",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "むかえます",
        "back": "go to meet, welcome, to receive",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "つかれます",
        "back": "get tired",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "だします\n「てがみを～」",
        "back": "send [letter]",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "はいります\n「きっさてんに～」",
        "back": "enter [a coffee shop]",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "でます\n「きっさてんを～」",
        "back": "go out [a coffee shop]",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "けっこんします",
        "back": "marry, get married",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいものします",
        "back": "do shopping",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいます",
        "back": "shopping",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょくじします",
        "back": "have a meal, dine",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "さんぽします\n「こえんを～」",
        "back": "take a walk [in a park]",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいへん\n「な」",
        "back": "hard, tough, severe, difficult",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほしい",
        "back": "want (something)",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "さびしい",
        "back": "lonely",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひろい",
        "back": "wide, spacious",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "せまい",
        "back": "narrow, small (room, area etc.)",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "しやくしょ",
        "back": "municipal office, city hall",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "プール",
        "back": "swimming pool",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "かわ",
        "back": "river",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいざい",
        "back": "economy",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "びじゅつ",
        "back": "fine arts",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "つり",
        "back": "fishing",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "スキー",
        "back": "skiing",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいぎ",
        "back": "meeting, conference",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "とうろく",
        "back": "registration",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅうまつ",
        "back": "weekend",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "～ごろ",
        "back": "around / about (point of time)",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "なにか",
        "back": "something",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "どこか",
        "back": "somewhere, some place",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "おなかがすきました",
        "back": "(I’m) hungry",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "おなかがいっぱいです",
        "back": "(I’m) full",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "のどがかわきました",
        "back": "(I’m) thirsty",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "そうですね",
        "back": "I agree with you",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "そうしましょう",
        "back": "Let’s do that. (Used when agreeing with someone’s suggestion)",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごちゅうもんは？",
        "back": "May I take your order?",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいしょく",
        "back": "Set Meal",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎゅうどん",
        "back": "Bowl of rice with beef",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "「しょうしょう」おまちくださいべつべつに",
        "back": "Please wait [a moment] Separately",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "みち",
        "back": "road",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    },
    {
        "front": "おります",
        "back": "to descend, to get off",
        "chapter": "N5 C13"
    }
]